debilitated venus
this position of venus has troubled a
lot of people
and the most impact that
i have seen is
basically in love relationship and
marriage
what debilitated winners do why
it gives impact to relationship and
marriage we will try to find that out in
this video
do not forget to hit like subscribe and
share and hit the bell icon so that you
never miss another update
if you want to follow me on social media
you can follow me the links are in the
description box below and if you want to
take my consultation
the email id is also in the description
box below so let's
start the video analysis for debilitated
[Music]
venus
venus in virgo
virgo is a sign of calculation
it's a sign ruled by mercury it's a sign
of
disputes fight it's a sign of argument
these are not the traits for love and
romance this is not a perfect
environment
if the love have fight if the love have
calculations if the relationship
is based on profit and loss give and
take which virgo means
then it's not a relationship it's not a
healthy relationship
that is why venus the planet of love
relationship
goes into the sign of virgo it does not
find
a suitable environment and when it
doesn't have a suitable environment
that's called debilitation
when venus goes into the sign of virgo
the couple of things happens here
first of all if you see from the khal
purush the second lord goes into sixth
house
so you know the kuttumba bhav goes into
dispute it shows family disputes
and then the seventh lord is twelfth
from itself
loss of marriage so when venus goes into
the sign of virgo
the maximum impact is on the marriage
and relationships
the way you talk the way things execute
with you
usually this happens because in the past
life
there are karmas associated with this
planet
that were not so good and that is why in
this life the planet is not comfortable
and making you deprived deprived of love
deprived of
emotions it can make you overly
practical it can make you
fearful of relationship fearful of
marriage and if mass is associated with
debilitated venus
it can increase the desire the lust in
the body
and it can never allow you to settle in
a relationship
venus has to be corrected when it is in
the sign of virgo
a debilitated venus needs your attempt
to sacrifice so whenever you have a this
position of venus this will ask you for
more sacrifices
so every time you will be in a
relationship or in a marriage you will
see
that it is not up to the mark or it is
not the way you wanted it to be
you are giving more than what you are
getting the emotions are not being met
the desires are not being met it is
somewhat
to the extreme either too less
or way too much for you to handle this
position of venus has to be handled
carefully otherwise this
has the potential to completely make the
relationship
go bad sour even make it a case of a
divorce
separation if rahu is associated
associated with this venus then really
it has the potential to malign this
venus in a way
that you will purposefully put yourself
into a situation
where things can go wrong where things
can go bad if ketu is with debilitated
venus
it seriously shows a very bad karma in
the past life
that can really deprive you of love
unless there is there are other factors
so if you have this and you don't really
it doesn't necessarily mean that exactly
this is what is going to happen
because hundreds of factors are included
in this
what if jupiter aspects it what if the
seventh lord is strong what is the
seventh lord is exalted
a lot of things matter here but what one
thing is for sure
that virgo venus will definitely make
you practical the experience that you
will get in life
in love and relationship will be such
that you would not really
be a hundred percent in that
relationship
maybe it's your mentality or maybe it's
the experience
the the issues that you face in the
relationship the issues that you face in
the marriage
that makes you a person like you are
the foremost thing that you should do
is respect the opposite gender
especially the men who have debilitated
venus find it
find very difficult to adjust with your
wife
even to get married to maintain a
relationship
and also sometimes they can they can get
maligned their images can get maligned
because of some
bad activity some bad karma
so the first thing is that you should
respect the opposite gender and
you should work towards improvement of
deprived females you should work for
female
welfare you should help
a school girl go to school one who is
deprived from going to school
you should help some somebody
to learn the lessons of life by going to
school by going to institution by going
to ashram
in whatever way you can because venus is
a guru before everything
he is a teacher he is a mentor
so when venus goes back he wants to
teach you through
a bad experience or solve relationships
so you have to give so when you have a
debilitated venus it means you have to
give to society
the more you give the more you get
and this also means that you cannot
expect anything in return
because if you expect anything in return
it will again become a lesson
so when you have a debilitated venus
it's like a free-flowing karma
you keep doing what you can do for other
people
and let them do what they can but you
should
not change your stand you should always
thrive to become
a better partner a better person a
better human being
and a person who will shower love even
if he is deprived because
venus is a water sign in virgo venus
goes dry
the love and emotions goes dry
that is another problem because if you
don't feel love if you don't feel
emotions then
how will you show or how will you
fulfill the emotional need of other
person
and at that time you should follow your
kartav you should follow your duty
you should do what's what's best you can
do and then leave everything
on god because at least you are doing
karma and if you are doing honest karma
you will get the karma full apart from
them this you can chant
the vishnu mantra om namo
both of this will help you getting the
maximum
out of this debilitated planet
and this also means that you will get
the love that you deserve one more
factor i would like to add in this case
is the position of venus in navamsha
and the position of venus through moon
if venus is really bad
in your lagna in the through the moon
sign
in the navamsha and you are undergoing
venus mahadasha
then the maximum negative effects can be
seen
otherwise it can be buffered it can be
filtered and it can be adjusted and
there are workarounds for this
i just wanted to explain the connection
between debilitated venus and a bad
relationship or marriage
in a very short way this is an academic
video
so take it as an academic video for
academic interest
and for upgrading the knowledge of vedic
astrology
thank you guys thank you for watching
astrology have a great day and do not
forget to like subscribe and share
and hit the bell icon so that you never
miss another update this is your host
puneet
[Music]
namaste
you